早上好  太太
Well, mornin', little missus!
想和敬畏上帝的男人们共进早餐吗
Care for some breakfast with some god-fearing men?
怎么了
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
你不想跟我们玩玩吗
Don't you want to spend a little time with us?
别听他的  女士
Don't listen to him, ma'am!
我到处都找不到你
You weren't anywhere.
你好像都没有上床睡觉
Didn't even look like you came to bed for one minute.
我有了个主意
I had this idea.
是挖掘机
It's a dredge.
是蒸汽式挖掘机
It's a steam dredge.
在过来的路上了
It's on its way to us.
随时可能到
Should be here any day now.
我们得把它改造成蒸汽铲
We'll have to convert it to a steam shovel.
今早我突然想到
Had a notion just this mornin'...
我可以做一个底盘
I could build an undercarriage--
你得睡觉  吃东西  或者...
You need to sleep and eat or...
我不知道要做什么
I don't know what.
你不明白
You don't understand.
你最好带威廉回家吧
Better take William on along home.
他不该出来  你也是
Shouldn't be out here. You neither.
我会回家的  你走吧
I'll be along. Go on.
只要七条菱形道岔就能到达顶峰
I know we can reach the summit in seven diagonal cuts.
这叫做"之字形路"  对吧
They're called "Switchbacks," all right?
我很熟悉这一概念
I'm familiar with the concept.
我是工程师  博汉南
I'm an engineer, Bohannon.
总工程师
Chief engineer.
你先别急着给我下命令
Before you start givin' me orders,
我是为杜兰特先生工作的
it's Mr. Durant I work for.
你为联太公司工作
You work for the Union Pacific.
我们的任务是铺好铁路
Our job is to get the railroad movin'.
我需要十二个人帮忙做出加固底盘
I need a dozen men to help fashion a reinforced chassis
-这样就可以  -你需要
- so I can-- - You need?
先生们
Gentlemen!
博汉南先生刚给我分配了工作  还有你的
Mr. Bohannon was just tellin' me what my job is. Yours too.
挖掘机随时都可能到  而我们还没有准备好
Dredge'll be here any day now and we ain't ready.
-他要求十个人  -是十二个
- He is requesting 10 men... - 12.
停止筑墙  去组装零件
To be taken off their labor on the wall to assemble parts.
还有造一辆车
And build a car.
我们有没有专门技术  来向工人们展示
And do we have the expertise to show the men
-要怎么做  -我有个想法
- how this is done? - I got a notion.
想法啊
A notion? Mm.
但是我需要借助德兰尼先生的专业知识
But I'll need Mr. Delaney's know-how.
你说呢
Well?
可以
It can be done.
如果十二个人可以将就的话
If you settle for 10.
等一下
Hold up!
我们走
Let's go!
我让你们等一下
I said stop the train right there!
该死
Damn it.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你坐下
Sit down.
让大伙儿下车
Pull the men off your train.
他们有新任务
They've been reassigned.
-谁说的  -我说的
- On whose say-so? - Mine!
你为什么不让我们走
What's this with pullin' my men?
带十个最厉害的下车  包括你
Take your ten best off the train, and you too.
-我需要你来负责  -负责什么
- I need you in charge. - Charge of what?
你要么一起来要么走人
Either you come or I take 'em without you.
不把滑动装置搞定就没法用了
Dead in the water until you get that slide off.
维吉尔
Virgil!
博汉南先生
Mr. Bohannon!
这些人不是该去铲石头吗
Shouldn't these men be out shovelin' rocks?
我也这么觉得
I been thinkin' the same thing.
好  我们把两辆货车
All right, we're gonna take them two freight trucks
安放到铁轨上
and set 'em on the rails.
这样就可以运挖掘机了
They'll hold the platform for the dredge.
你以为我们有钢铁厂吗
You think we got an ironworks here?
-这里又不是芝加哥  -因为重量增加
- We ain't in Chicago. - You best build new bolsters
所以最好用新垫板和中心立轴
and kingpins for the extra weight.
今早我看了下  应该是这样的
I had a look this mornin', figure it's somethin' like this.
你明白吗  我们只修坏掉的东西
You hear me? We fix what's broke and that's all.
根本没人手帮我做那个
I barely got the manpower for that.
人手我给你带来了
Oh, I brought you the manpower.
我说的是技术工人
I'm talkin' about skilled labor.
-帕萨姆  -我的人可以学
- Psalms? - My men'll learn.
他们有人以前是种地轧棉花的呢
Some of them worked on ploughs and cotton gins where they from.
火车车厢可不是轧棉机
Railroad cars ain't cotton gins.
你应该听到他说的话了吧
And I think you heard him.
他们可以学
They can learn.
眼见为实
I'll believe it when I see it.
准备开工
Get her in position.
那里那个人
Man right there?
以为你只擅长挖渠开沟
Thinks all you good for is diggin' ditches.
你想证明他错了吗
You wanna prove him wrong?
我知道你看到我时看到的是什么
I know what you see when you look at me.
我看未必
Doubt that.
杀害埃兰的凶手
The man who killed Elam.
但那不是埃兰
But that wasn't Elam.
你我认识的那个人  永远不会回来了
The one you and me knew. He never come back.
我就只想说这么多
That's all I'm gonna say about it.
不再多说
Now or ever.
我会让我的人在维吉尔手下好好干活
I see to it my crew give Virgil no reason to complain.
安放车轮时注意安全
Y'all watch your feet mountin' them wheels now.
你现在想好要怎么办了吗
You thought about what you're gonna do now?
我是说  你想回家了吗
I mean, will you go home now?
圣路易斯
St. Louis.
什么
What?
圣路易斯
St. Louis.
那是我家
That's home.
但我在那没家人了
But I got no one there.
没有家人  一无所有
No one and nothin'.
不  不是的
No, that ain't true.
你识字
You can read.
会讲话
You talk nice.
脸蛋也漂亮
You got a pretty face.
你不用做妓女的
You don't have to be a whore.
你可以找更好的职业
You can be somethin' better.
你不明白
You don't know.
不做这个可能会更糟  这我明白
Could be a lot worse, I know that.
在我嫁给埃兰之前
Before I was with Elam--
埃兰
Elam.
我帮你在夏安镇找到工作前  和我住
Stay with me till we find you somethin' to do in Cheyenne.
我们一起想办法
We'll think on it together.
-早上好  -早上好
- Mornin'. - Mornin'.
您的电报
For you.
他们在内布拉斯加找到了海柯德的尸体
They found Heckard's body in Nebraska.
躺在铁路边上
By the side of the track.
有人打碎了他脑袋
Somebody bashed his head in.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
我们是在怎样的一个地方  艾特伍德
What kind of a place have we found ourselves in, Atwood,
美国联邦法警的性命
Where the life of a U.S. Marshal
会被一只妄自尊大的癞蛤蟆
can be snuffed out at the whim of an arrogant,
凭一时意气夺走
pompous, self-important toad?
杜兰特吗
Durant?
源头不治理
Shit flows downstream.
哪来清河水
From the headwaters.
娜奥米
Naomi?
驾
Whoa.
站住
Hold it right there!
告诉海彻神父他女儿来了
Tell Father Hatch his daughter's at the gate!
海彻兄弟
Brother Hatch!
吁
Ho.
感觉我们走了很久了
Feels a long time since we've been here.
并没有
It wasn't.
但感觉很像
Feels like it, though.
赞美上帝
Oh, god be praised!
看看他
Oh, look at him.
博汉南兄弟
Brother Bohannon.
-海彻神父  -进来呀
- Father Hatch. - Well, come in.
-干嘛站在外面  -主教呢
- Why are we stayin' out here? - The bishop?
他早不在了  不用担心他
Ah. He's long gone, you needn't worry about him.
你们赶了那么多路
Now, you've been traveling.
又累又饿吧
You're tired and hungry.
你妈一定很高兴
Your momma's gonna be so happy.
驾
Come on.
在这等着
Wait here.
作为死刑犯  你看起来很轻松嘛
You look rather cavalier for a man who's set to hang.
你很喜欢这么目无法纪吗
Is it your habit to take the law of the land so lightly?
一个州长跑到这种地方
Ain't the usual thing for a Governor
跟一个死刑犯谈话  真不寻常
to come down here and conversate with condemned fugitives.
我问你是不是目无法纪
I'm askin' if you hold the law in contempt.
法律和我互相为难对方
The law and me have been at each other pretty hard
已经很久啦
for a long time now.
我们互相了解
We know each other well.
你有特殊的技能  斯诺先生
You have certain skills, Mr. Snow.
我也许需要你的技能
I may have need for those skills.
问题是你能否把那些技能
The question is whether you can put them to use for someone
传授给别人
other than yourself.
这我可从来没试过
I have never tried.
你替我工作  我救你的命怎么样
What if it were worth your life?
你发誓执行怀俄明州的法律
Do you swear to enforce the law of Wyoming,
其文字和精神
its letter and its spirit,
执行公务  不存偏见
without prejudice of persons in pursuance of your duties?
是的  我发誓
Right, yeah. I do.
那么你是新法警了
Then you're our new marshal.
很多人都会吃惊的
Lots of individuals would be surprised.
夏安镇有很多其他地方的通缉犯
Cheyenne's full of men wanted elsewhere.
逃保者  亡命徒
Bail jumpers, fugitives.
铁路工人中还有契约自由人
Also indentured freedmen among the railroad workers,
游民无赖
vagrants.
杜兰特几年没付过他们债券了
Durant hasn't paid their bond in years.
也就是说他们也是非法的
That means they're illegal too.
我要你逮捕所有这些人
I want you to arrest them all.
-我需要几位副官  -就是他们了
- Gonna need some deputies. - Take those.
该死  伙计们  今天是你们的幸运日
Damn, boys, it's your lucky day.
敢违反我的命令
Travel one inch outside my orders,
我就亲手吊死你
I'll tie the noose myself.
别担心  州长
Not to worry, Governor.
能为你做事很荣幸
My honor.
绅士地握个手吧
As a gentleman.
从这些人开始
You start with those.
夏洛特会做饭  洗衣服  做家务
Charlotte can cook, wash, keep house.
她很会算账
Does her figures like anything.
擅长读写
She can read and write like nobody's business.
大家能看出她是个体面的人
Folks can see she's a respectable person.
我们会给你一身替换的衣服
We'll get you a change of clothes.
我会在这给你找点活儿干
I'll find something for you to do here.
我简直不能想象你经历了什么
Can't even imagine what you've been through.
谢...
Thank--
没事的
It's okay.
谢谢您
Thank you.
他的眼睛像他爸
He's got eyes like his papa.
他难道没继承博汉南兄弟那双漂亮的眼睛吗
Don't he have brother Bohannon's pretty eyes?
你居然敢说我老公眼睛漂亮
How dare you say that about my husband.
以丝特已经有自己的男人了
Esther's got her own beau.
迈克尔·杜恩兄弟
Brother Michael Doone.
他的眼睛好像晒太阳的老公牛似的
He's got eyes like an old ox sittin' in the sun.
姑娘们
Girls.
这可是娜奥米回家来的第一顿饭
This is Naomi's first meal home.
她跟她们在一起很开心
She's happy to be among them.
她想念这种生活
She's missed this.
这是事实
That's a fact.
我想我猜的到是什么让你离开夏安镇
Well, I can only guess at what's brought you
回到了这里
back from Cheyenne.
但是难道没有什么能让你留下的理由吗
But is there any good reason you shouldn't stay on?
你们俩一起
Both of you, together.
留在我们身边
With us.
现在这里我说了算
I have authority here.
我可以帮你在公理会说说话
I can smooth your way with the congregation.
大家会欢迎你的
You will be made welcome.
也许达森主教真的是对的
Perhaps bishop dutson was right after all.
怎么说
How's that?
一个正义之人所能有的最高期许都能
Only that everything a righteous man could ever want
在这里找到
is here.
你那话什么意思  达森走了  去哪了
What'd you mean, Dutson's gone? Gone where?
因为布里格姆·杨
Brigham Young.
去了犹他州
To Utah.
你父亲希望我们留下来
Your father wants us to stay on for good.
你还没明确表态是否愿意
You still ain't said if that's what you want.
我连想都不愿想回去的事
I can't think about goin' back.
娜奥米
Naomi.
我们在这里过得更好
We're better off here.
我和威廉  别跟我说你没看出来
Me and William, and don't say that you don't see that.
你在夏安镇过得不好
You ain't had it easy in Cheyenne.
我知道的  行吗
I know that, all right?
我真的知道
I do.
但夏安镇也不会一直如此的
But it ain't always gonna be Cheyenne.
铁路会延续  我们也
The railroad'll move on, we'll--
不是因为夏安镇
This isn't about Cheyenne!
我洗去了你衣上的血迹
I washed the blood off of you.
洗去了一个被你杀掉的
Washed the blood off of you of a man
你很敬爱的人的血迹
that you killed, that you loved.
我永远不会忘记
I ain't forgettin' that.
这就是你
That's you.
真实的你
That's who you are.
终点到了  各位
End of the line, folks!
夏安镇  终点站
Cheyenne. End of the line.
通缉令
让我瞧瞧  老伙计
What we got here, old timer?
你们几个
Y'all go ahead around
从那些货车后面绕过去  懂吗
the back side of those wagons over there, yeah?
-是  长官  -你听到命令了
- Yes, sir. - You heard him.
起
Hup!
没错  哥们儿
That's it, brother.
铁匠铺
把它对齐
Even that out.
起
Hup!
往上点  哥们儿
Get it on up, brother.
放进去
Get it in there.
没错  各位
That's it, folks.
所有人
All you men!
看来你们中有些人是通缉犯
It appears some of you are wanted by the law.
有些是没有债券的非法劳工
Else you're here on bonds that ain't been paid.
我是来逮捕你们  主持正义的
I am here to see that y'all are brought to justice.
你们少给我点麻烦  这事也就好过去
Less trouble you give me, easier it'll be.
当然啦  我也不怕麻烦
'course, I don't mind trouble.
所有这些人  所有的
All of these men, all of 'em,
都是联太公司的合法劳工
Are legitimate employees of the Union Pacific Railroad.
长官
Sir.
通缉  悬赏200美元
维吉尔·法恩斯沃思
Virgil Farnsworth.
在纽约被通缉
Wanted in New York.
那是一次酒吧斗殴
It was a bar fight
就在波威里街上[纽约街名]
down at the Bowery.
其他肇事者走开了
Other guy walked away.
你们难道不考虑这点吗
Don't that count for nothin'?
达奇·杜弗雷
Dutch Dufray.
在博爱城[费城别称]武装抢劫
Armed robbery in the city of brotherly love!
任何阻拦我们的人
Anybody gets in our way,
一并抓起来
you arrest them too.
现在...瞧瞧还有谁
Now...Who do we have here?
朱利叶斯·汉凯
Julius Hankey.
瞧瞧那孩子跑的
Look at that boy run.
伊诺克·布尔
Enoch Buell.
帕萨姆·杰克逊
Psalms Jackson.
杜兰特没给我付钱
Durant didn't pay my bond.
你为什么不逮捕他
Why don't you arrest him?
有可能会哦
It might come to that.
走
Move.
走吧
Come on!
就这样  就这些了
That's it, that's all.
把这些人都抓起来  先生们  跟我来
Round up the goodies, gentlemen. Follow me.
滚出去  没错
Get outta here! That's right!
放什么屁  我没抢过任何人
What kind of cra-- I never robbed nobody!
至少没在俄亥俄州抢过
Not in Ohio anyways!
我才不在乎那张通缉令上写了什么呢
I don't care what the poster says!
我们会把你拖到法官面前的
We gonna drag you down to the judge,
你到他面前去叨叨吧
and you can talk his ear off.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
字母"I"是...
"I" Is for...
岛...岛屿
Is--is-land?
-岛屿  -岛屿
- Island. - Island.
岛屿坐落在海上
That sits in the sea.
字母"J"是...
"J" is for...
胡...狼
Jack-kal?
-胡狼  -胡狼
- Jackal! - Jackal.
胡狼从树上蹿出
That springs from the tree.
字母"K"是...
"K" is a...
露丝  我有事相求
Ruth! I'm in need.
米奇
Mickey?
我需要一个地方容身  一个藏身之地
I need a place to stay, to hide.
我被通缉了
I'm a wanted man.
他们现在来追捕我了
They're coming now.
你瞧我这儿有个孩子呢
You see I have a child here.
你居然带着一把枪到礼拜的地方来
You come with a gun to a place of worship?
这也是我救了你一命的地方
The place I saved your life.
至于枪的问题
As for a gun,
假如你帮我  我就不打算用它了
I've no mind to use it if you help me.
我没有地方藏你
I have nowhere to hide you.
这次我要亲自上了  伙计们
I believe I'll take this myself, boys.
真他妈漂亮啊
Hot damn.
我以后得常来教堂
I got to go to church more often.
有什么可以效劳的吗
Can I help you?
我可以想到成千上百种你效劳的方式
Well, I can think of a thousand ways you could,
亲爱的  但是这次
darlin', but for now...
我们在找这些人
we're just lookin' for these men.
这里只有我和孩子
It's just me and the boy.
你要知道对联邦法警撒谎
You know lyin' to a federal marshal
不仅仅是罪过  而且违法
ain't just a sin, it's a felony.
这里没人
There's no one here.
不信你自己看
You see for yourself.
我还没看后面呢
I ain't seen what's back there yet.
满意了吗
Satisfied?
我这人不会轻易满意
I don't satisfy easy.
我会为了你和宝宝回来的
I'm comin' back for you and the baby.
光说没用
Don't say it.
我会的
I will.
那就等你回来时再见吧
I'll see you when you do it.
好的
Yeah.
帕默小姐把你打扮的很漂亮
Miss Palmer done you up real nice.
这身打扮能让你觉得不同
It can make you feel different.
感觉更好
Better.
我都忘记这种感觉了
I'd forgotten.
帕默夫人让我在饭厅做事
Mrs. Palmer put me to work in the dining room.
可笑的是你整天服侍人进餐自己就没胃口了
Funny how you lose your appetite servin' food all day.
有些事我不得不跟你讲
There's somethin' I have to say to you,
因为我之前一直失魂落魄
since I haven't been myself.
什么事
What?
我忘了要感谢你
I've forgotten to thank you.
还有些别的事
There's somethin' else as well.
是关于埃兰的
It's about Elam.
我知道你一直想谈谈他
I know you've wanted to talk about him.
听别人说  他
From what people say, he...
他并不一直是我知道的那种人
he wasn't always the man I knew.
不  他以前不是的
No, he wasn't.
我现在知道了
I know that now.
也知道你爱他
And you loved him.
我想让你知道我相信他想念的
Then I want you to know that I believe it was you
那人是你
he was thinkin' of.
找寻的那人也是你
And lookin' for.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know!
他逮捕了我们重要的修路人手
He's arrested our key railroad men.
都用的是莫须有的或很早以前的罪行
All on trumped up charges or crimes long forgotten.
我们要如何应对
What exactly are we doin' about it?
我要做我之前就应该做的事
I'll do what I should've done before:
我要任命你为铁路警察总长
I'll make you chief of railroad police,
拥有赎回我们劳工的权利
with authority to reclaim our workforce.
去要求他们放人
Insist they be released!
铁路警徽对坎贝尔没有用
Railroad badge won't mean nothin' to Campbell.
他是联邦政府的人
He's federal.
他的警徽对铁路也没用
So is the railroad.
妈的  我需要你  博汉南
Damn it, I need you, Bohannon.
我需要你的枪
I need your gun.
我发现你已经不再佩枪了
I see you aren't even wearing one anymore.
对它失去兴趣了
Lost my taste for it.
你他妈还真会挑时间扮圣人啊
Well, you picked one hell of a time to turn saint!
你被捕了
You are under arrest.
罪名是谋杀联邦法警德怀特·海柯德
For the murder of Dwight Heckard federal marshal.
你是新任法警吗
You're the new marshal?
我自己也是大吃一惊
You know, it surprised the hell out of me too.
别碰我
Take your hands off me!
不用给他戴手铐
He don't need to be cuffed.
他要是反抗  倒是帮了我大忙
He'd be doin' me a favor if he puts up a fight.
你也是  博汉南
You too, Bohannon.
如我所言  博汉南  挑得真是时候
Like I said, Bohannon, one hell of a time!
进去吧  光鲜绅士
In you go, fancy man.
这里充满了主的平和
The lord's peace is upon this place.
我感受到了  兄弟
I feel it, brother!
既然我们旅行至此休息
While we rest here from travel...
你能否告诉我你到底是谁
you may tell me who you are.
我知道你不是达森
I know you are not Dutson.
没错
Mm, it's true.
我叫安德森
My name is Anderson.
有一天我偶然目睹了悲剧的一幕
I came upon a tragic scene one day.
达森主教和他的妻子孩子被印第安人杀死
Bishop Dutson, his wife and child lying slaughtered
陈尸河边
by Indians beside a river.
当我为他们做祷告时  我感受到了神启
As I prayed over them, I received a message--
来自天父的信息
Message from heavenly father--
告诉我应当顶替这个可怜人的身份
That I should take this unfortunate man's identity
完成他的使命
and do his bidden work.
如果我做错了
If I have done wrong.
你现在还在跟我说谎就是错的
You have done wrong by lying to me now.
天父赋予了我明辨是非的洞察力
Heavenly father endowed me with the spirit of discernment.
重新说
Begin again.
我发誓
I swear...
我是个摩门教徒
that I am mormon
我的信仰十分坚定
and my faith is strong.
那达森一家是怎么回事
And what then of the Dutsons?
我发现他们的时候
When I found them...
他们还活着
they were alive.
我再说一次  那是上帝的指示
I say again, it was a sign from god.
他的意志
His will
告诉我应该夺走他们俗世的性命
that I should take their earthly lives
然后顶替达森的名字
and d-drape myself in Dutson's name
和肉身
and person.
之后  我竭尽全力
Thereafter, I did all I could to--
侍奉他
to honor him.
在史密斯保卫站想尽一切办法
In every way at Fort Smith.
我现在说的一切都是真的
Everything I have said now is true.
我很感激我有幸被指引
I'm thankful that my path has led me to--
获得神圣的权利  去协助...
to the sacred privilege of aiding in...
协助你的工作
aiding in your work.
我相信你很懊悔
I do believe in your remorse,
也相信你在寻求宽恕
and that you seek forgiveness.
太好了
Good.
没错
I do.
没错  没错
I do. I do.
没错
I do.
那你到底叫什么名字
And what is your name?
我
I...
我叫托尔·刚德森
I am Thor Gundersen.
来自挪威
Of Norway.
那么
Well...
来自挪威的托尔·刚德森
Thor Gundersen of Norway.
你可以和我走
You may go forward with me
重新开始生活
and begin life again.
但是我们要去哪
But where shall we go?
时间自会揭晓
Time will reveal.
我在夏安镇很少有喜欢的东西
Few things I find pleasant in Cheyenne.
这红酒算一个
But this wine's one.
你还喜欢什么
What else?
喝酒时坐在你对面
Sittin' across from you while I drink it.
我同意
I agree.
酒的确好喝
About the wine.
现在
Now...
我没想到会在这里遇到你这样的女士
You are not the kind of lady I expected to find out here.
为什么像你这样久经世故的东海岸女子
How is it that an east coast sophisticate like yourself
会沦落到边疆城镇
ends up in a frontier town
和大话家杜兰特
Surrounded by charlatans like Durant,
流氓米奇·麦克吉尼斯
Ruffians like Mickey McGinnes...
以及被解职的南方佬博汉南在一起
And a defrocked Johnny Reb like Bohannon?
你忘说西德尼·斯诺了
I notice you forgot to mention Sidney Snow.
一个枪击商店
How does a man who shoots up a store
射杀男孩的人  怎么会戴上法警徽章
and kills a young boy end up wearing a Marshal's badge?
你为什么把徽章给他
And how do you justify giving it to him?
问得好  埃里森女士
Good question, Miss Ellison.
博汉南先生
Mr. Bohannon.
你打扰我们用餐了
You're interrupting our dinner.
我想听到你的回答
I aim to hear your answer.
一个被格兰特任命  致力恢复法律和秩序的人
How's a man appointed by Grant to bring law and order
怎么会把徽章给西德尼·斯诺这样的疯狗
put a badge on a mad dog like Sidney Snow,
他就是疯狗  我们都知道
And that's what he is, we both know it.
我很幸运能招入他这样的人
I'm just lucky I had a man like him to put a badge on.
这个镇子的暴力已经夺走了我的两位法警
I've lost two marshals to violence in this town,
不用再失去更多人  我便已经明白
And I don't need to lose more to know that I'm a long way
在这里不能用和平手段重塑法律与秩序
from being able to use peaceful means to bring "Law and order,"
正如你所说
As you put it.
我觉得新法警的手段
I think my new marshal's methods
很适合这里
exactly fit the bill.
西德尼带来的不是法律和秩序
What Sidney's bringing ain't law and order,
人都被抓进监狱了  我没法铺铁路
and I can't build a railroad with them men in jail.
铁路和其他的事必须等等
Then the railroad and everything else will have to wait
直到我驯服这座镇子
until I bring this town to heel.
我说得明白点吧  坎贝尔先生
Let me spell it out for you, Mr. Campbell.
放了囚犯们
Release them prisoners.
我只说一次
I'm only askin' you once.
如果这是威胁  我就当没听见
If that's a threat, I didn't hear it.
现在  你能让女士和我继续用餐了吗
Now would you let this lady and me go on with our dinner?
你要记住
You remember:
我先礼貌地问过你
I asked you as a gentleman first.
埃里森女士
Miss Ellison.